感谢Veto，是时候
Thanks Veto.
And now it's time
将我们的Sunshine App安装到手机上了
to install the Sunshine app
on our phones.
找一根USB线
So to get started,
let's grab a USB cable.
连接手机和电脑，另外我们需要开启USB debugging
We'll plug in our device and then
we'll need to enable USB debugging.
可以在Setting中的开发者选项中找到
This can be found in Developer options
in the Settings app.
不过在4.2以上版本
But note that on Android
devices 4.2 and above,
这个选项是默认隐藏的
the option is actually hidden by default.
要开启它的话，进入Setting
To find the secret menu,
go to the Settings app.
滚到最下面的About Phone
Scroll down to About Phone.
然后滚动到最下面的Build Number
Then go down to Build Number
单击7次
and tap on that seven times.
然后，当你回到Setting
Then, when you go back to Settings,
就会看到开发者选项菜单出现了
you'll see the Developer
options menu appear.
另外，也要设置你的电脑让其检测到你的设备
Also, set up your computer
to detect your device.
阅读下面的笔记来了解详情
Check the instructor notes
for more details.
我们后面会继续用物理设备
We're going to continue
using a device because it's faster
因为这样开发起来更快更流畅，不过如果你没有也没关系
and smoother for development.
But if you don't have one, that's okay.
你也可以一直用之前创建的模拟器
You can continue using the emulator
that we created previously.